=The Truth (Season 4)=
(Behind-the-Scenes Cast Interview)
(Wu Bi as Mr. Wu)
While waiting backstage,
(Pai Xiaoxuan as Pai)
which player stood out as being
quiet or outgoing?
I heard Ding singing
"Love Overcomes Everything"
downstairs yesterday.
(I was indeed singing)
So I thought he must
be quite outgoing.
They also seem very close
to one another,
so I do not think any of them
are particularly quiet.
(Quite perceptive)
They are all very outgoing.
Yes.
What about you, Mr. Wu?
(The butler is exasperated)
They are simply so loud.
(Joining the group immediately)
Not noisy.
Just very lively.
What's it to you?
(Don't forget your identity)
We're an prestigious family.
Exactly.
Are we not all...
(Desperately trying to save face)
None of us are related by blood.
We are an elite family.
They're so loud
I can't hear
my earpiece.
(Worried about all the heirs)
Will the helicopter fit us all?
It will.
Two can hang outside.
Okay.
We could lower
the ladder
(Watching silently)
and stand on it.
Ning could hang outside like this.
Very lively indeed.
Did you deliberately set up jokes
for the players during filming?
How did they react?
I feel that some romantic scenes
may have been incorporated
into the script.
Ding.
(Huh?)
What's with the car?
There is absolutely nothing between us.
(That was a close one!)
He has never given me
any high-fashion dresses.
What?
(What a bold one)
Nor has he ever
personally written his name on my arm.
His name.
(Ding)
What?
(That was explosive)
(His name)
(The next part is even more explosive)
Sir, I am sorry.
But what am I to do?
As a capable maid,
my body can carry sacks of rice
and tanks of gas,
but it cannot withstand
the way my heart aches for you.
He is firing straight into my heart.
How is the situation
concerning Uncle Er?
We're investigating.
There's a new development.
All right. I am putting her to sleep.
I will come find you once she is asleep.
What if she discovers our relationship?
Do not worry.
I can handle her completely.
So, earlier,
the investigators asked me
that if I had to choose
between the two young masters,
which one I might prefer.
Between He and Ding,
which one is truly your beloved?
I have to choose one?
As an adult, I refuse to choose.
I want them both.
(They are all beloved)
I deeply
regret that answer now.
I do not know if I am allowed
to say this,
but privately, I actually
prefer Zhou Keyu.
(An Ke, Fifth Young Master of An family)
Could this be the legendary
dream,Uncle Ke?
So at the time, I said,
"As an adult, I refuse to choose".
"I want them both".
But once I came downstairs,
I wondered, why did I not say
I wanted Mr. Ke?
(Completely devoted to Mr. Ke)
I regretted it the moment
I came downstairs.
Did you incorporate your comedic
skills into today's performance?
Skills?
The skill was essentially
to keep thinking of jokes in case
they asked me some difficult questions.
I was afraid it'd get awkwardly quiet.
Yes, it probably helped a little.
How was being an NPC
on a variety show different
from your previous work?
Theater is fully rehearsed
before being performed on stage.
During rehearsals, however,
you have more freedom
to move around and more control
over the environment.
What about you, Pai?
I suppose I had to stay
a little more focused.
Over the past few days,
I've been thinking about my role.
(Well prepared)
I was worried
that when the players
questioned me, I might not
know how to respond
or might disrupt
the atmosphere
and compromise my character.
(Fully committed to the role)
So I had to stay more focused.
When I normally film my own content,
because it is my own work,
I am comfortable
with it and do not feel
nearly as much pressure.
(He Jinghao as Cameraman He)
Did the players ever make you
break character?
It happened at the end,
when Ms. Jin said, "Why don't
we silence them permanently?"
(That was terrifying)
So I immediately ran away.
Which player would you most
like to exchange identities with?
Ms. Jin.
Why?
Because she is very entertaining.
(Of course)
She's very good at the game.
=The Truth (Season 4)=
(SVIP: New episodes Wed & Thu at 12 PM)
(VIP: Next-day access at 12 PM,
one week early)